Welcome to this module, you learned so much about react, redux and all the core features of both libraries.
Witaj w tym module, nauczye si duo o reakcji, reduxie i wszystkich podstawowych funkcjach obu bibliotek.
We built an amazing application with all these tools.
Zbudowalimy niesamowit aplikacj z wszystkimi tymi narzdziami.
But one thing is missing, one thing that is not really related to react necessarily but what you have
Ale jednej rzeczy brakuje, jedna rzecz, ktra nie jest tak naprawd zwizana z koniecznoci reagowania, ale
in a lot of applications, authenticating users.
z tym, co masz w wielu aplikacjach, uwierzytelniajcych uytkownikw.
And I want to show you how this would work in a react single page application, single page application
Chc ci pokaza, jak to bdzie dziaa w aplikacji pojedynczej strony, ktra reaguje
because if you have a multi-page application where you render different pages for different requests
na jedn stron, poniewa jeli masz aplikacj wielostronicow, w ktrej renderujesz
from your server, you handle authentication in the traditional way of having a session on the server
rne strony dla rnych da z twojego serwera, obsugujesz uwierzytelnianie w tradycyjny sposb sesja
and returning different pages after checking the validity of the user or the authentication status on
na serwerze i zwracanie rnych stron po sprawdzeniu wanoci uytkownika lub statusu uwierzytelnienia
the server.
na serwerze.
Now the special thing about authentication in react is that you have only one file and thereafter, you
Teraz szczegln rzecz w uwierzytelnianiu jest to, e masz tylko jeden plik, a
get no new file,
potem nie dostajesz
so you can check the authentication status of the user on the server but not on every request, at least
nowego pliku, wic moesz sprawdzi status uwierzytelnienia uytkownika na serwerze, ale nie na kadym daniu, przynajmniej nie
not in the traditional model.
w tradycyjnym modelu .
So that is what we'll have a look at, how does this work in react
Oto, na co mamy rzuci okiem, jak to
and of course, we'll also implement authentication in our burger project.
dziaa, a my oczywicie wdroymy uwierzytelnianie w naszym projekcie z burgerami.